Guide to the Pennsylvania State University, Department of Animal Nutrition records 00044
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- Notebooks/Record Books, 7
  - Notebook #530 - Spray Treatments, 1938 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #567 - Tree Treatments, 1946 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #579 - Toxicity Tests, 1949 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #546 - Apple Tests, 1942 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #545 - Cherry Leaves, 1942 (Box 44)
  - Notebook #413-Hay, undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #414-Samples, 1928-1929 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #253-Calf Feeding Experiment, 1902-1903 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #166-Tests (Wilson), 1902 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #350 (Kuhlmonn), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #509-Fat Content, undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #348-Spring Season (Erb), 1915 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #150-Lab (Carpenter), 1901 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #132 - Feeding Stuffs (Sample Slips), 1900 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #124-Letters, 1898 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #134-Lab (Carter), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #351-Samples, undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #123-Lab, undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #122-Lab (Way), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #129-Lab (Beistle), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #408-Food, 1932-1933 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #130-Fertilizers (McDonell), 1899 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #121-Sugar Beet Record (Hiester), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #152-Samples (Brown), 1902 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #145-Fertilizer (Pingree), 1901 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #157 (Norris), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #159-Samples (Pingree), 1902 (Box 45)
  - Notebook #000-Lab (Thompson), 1903 (Box 45)
  - Notebook # 119 (C.P. Bristle), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook # 125 (C.P. Bristle), 1899 (Box 45)
  - Notebook # 127 (Brown and Pingree), 1899 (Box 45)
  - Notebook # 128 (C.W. Norris), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook # 151 (W.J. Carter and R.O. Brooks), undated (Box 45)
  - Notebook #103 - Package Record, 1897 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #107 - Samples (Hutchinson), undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #113 - Samples (Sweetser), undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #344 - Crop Reports, 1915-1919 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #105 - Milk Book (Norris), 1896 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #111 - Samples (Norris), 1897 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #283 - Weather Reports, 1910 (Box 47)
  - Notebook N91 - Chemical Lab Bill for State Board of Ag/State Dept of Ag, 1896 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #293 - Lab (Crawford), undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #292 - Lab, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #90 - Herd Tests, 1896 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #93 - Machine Statistics, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #107 - Tobacco Experiment (Fries), 1897 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #300 - Lab, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #170 - Samples (Darrow), undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #345 - Samples (Thomas), undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #328 - Lab (Caldwell), undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #295 - Lab, 1912 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #342 - Samples, 1915 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #340 - Samples, 1915 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #325 - Samples, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #302 - Lab, 1913 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #296 - Lab, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #281 - Samples, 1911-1912 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #000-Milk Tests, 1898 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #288 - Samples, 1911 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #98 - Samples (McDonnell), 1889 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #291 - Lab (Thomas), 1912 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #332 - Lab, 1915 (Box 47)
  - Notebook N7 - Lab Notes (Frear), 1901 (Box 47)
  - Notebook N86 - Lab (McDonnell), 1895 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #88 - Cattle Tests, 1896 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #106 - Samples (Brown), undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #101 - Lab (Norris), 1896 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #296 - Lab, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #347 - Lab, 1915 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #327 - Lab, 1913 (Box 47)
  - Notebook #343 - Samples, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #341 - Samples, undated (Box 47)
  - Notebook #20-Samples (Fries), 1889 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #70 - Size and Number of Fat Globules in Milk, 1892 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #77 - Samples - Fertilizer (E.J. Haley), 1893 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #18-Samples (Fries), 1889 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #79-Moisture, undated (Box 51)
  - Notebook #66-Samples, 1895 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #00-K 2 O (Sweetser), 1890 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #73-Samples, 1895 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #155 - Tobacco Experiment, 1904 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #158 - Hessian Fly Experiments (Exp. 205), 1906 (Box 51)
  - NoteBook #157 - Pole-Bum Experiment, 1905 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #19-Samples, undated (Box 51)
  - Notebook #00 - Moisture (Sweetser), undated (Box 51)
  - Notebook #72 - Fertilizer Samples (Fries), 1892 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #78-Viseisity of Milk (Fries), 1893 (Box 51)
  - Notebook N8 - Bone Fertilizers, undated (Box 51)
  - Notebook #64-Potash Determinations (Sweetser), 1893 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #134 - Commerical Feeding Stuff, 1904 (Box 51)
  - Notebook N60 - Experiments, 1891 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #60-Butter Fat Notes (Haley), undated (Box 51)
  - Notebook N76 - Samples (McDonnell) (Books 1 and 2), 1894 (Box 51)
  - Notebook N75 - Samples, 1897 (Box 51)
  - Notebook N59 - Milk Samples, 1890 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #59-Milk Samples (Sweetser and Fields), 1893-1894 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #22-Evaporation Records, 1888 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #80-Samples (Field), 1894 (Box 51)
  - Notebook #172 - Tobacco Experiment, 1907-1909 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #173 - Analysis, 1912-1914 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #174 - Samples, 1908-1909 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #175 - Samples, 1914 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #177 - Samples, 1909-1910 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #179 - Analysis, 1916 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #180 - Wholesale Prices from Oil, Paint and Drug Reporter, 1910 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #183 - Soil Tests with Fertilizer on Corn and Potatoes, 1906 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #184 - Timothy Hay Cooperative Experiment, 1907 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #185 - Experiment Stations Countrywide, 1914-1917 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #186 - Analysis, 1914-1915 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #187 - Analysis, 1915-1916 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #190, 1917 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #191 - Samples, 1918-1919 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #192 - Samples, 1919 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #193 - Analysis, 1920 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #194 - Limestone, 1921-1922 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #195 - Analysis, 1922-1925 (Box 49)
  - Notebook #196 - Analysis, 1925-1932 (Box 49)
  - Notebook R40 - Digestibility of Ensilage Corn, 1892 (Box 46)
  - Notebook R41 - Maintenance Feeding of Steers, 1892-1893 (Box 46)
  - Notebook R42 - Tobacco Experiments, 1893 (Box 46)
  - Notebook R43 - Feeding of Milk and Butterfat, 1893-1894 (Box 46)
  - Notebook R44 - Digestion Work, 1893-1894 (Box 46)
  - Notebook #150, 1911-1918 (Box 2)
  - Notebook - Iodine Project with Potato's, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Calorimeter Log Book, 1905-1911 (Box 2)
  - Iron, Moisture, Nitrogen Log Book, 1927-1928 (Box 27)
  - Record Book of Experiments 1 (Eastern Experiment Farm), 1868-1871 (Box 40)
  - Air Dry Book, 1928 (Box 30)
  - Record Book, 1889 (Box 53)
  - Agent's Sampling Book - (AG. Experiment Station), undated (Box 54)
  - Inventory Book, 1887-1889 (Box 54)
  - Farm Record Book - (Farmer's High School), 1869-1883 (Box 56)
  - Record Book of Experiments 3, 1872-1877 (Box 56)
  - Plot Book, 1869-1881 (Box 57)
  - Record of Plots, 1872-1875 (Box 40)
  - Record Book of Crops and Plots, 1870-1874 (Box 40)
- Photographs, 8
  - Photographs - Workroom/Building (oversized), undated (Box 58)
  - Photographs: Erie County Agricultural History, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Tools and Equipment (Unidentified), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Tools and Equipment (Identified) - (includes negatives), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Equipment/Tools/Machines, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: People Working, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Plants and Trees, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: AG Shows, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Classrooms and other Instructional Settings, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Animals, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Buildings and Rooms (unidentified), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Buildings (identified), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: People and Places (identified), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Groups (unidentified), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Instruction and Demonstrations, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Exhibitions and Displays, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Future Farmers of America, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Future Farmers of America (unidentified), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: and Negatives - PA. Association of the Future Farmers of America (unidentified), 1955 (Box 37)
  - Photographs: People (unidentified), undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Negatives, undated (Box 37)
  - Photographs: Farmlands (unidentified locations), undated (Box 37)
  - Photo Scrapbook - European Tour, 1929 (Box 57)
  - Photographs of animals and experiments, undated (Box 86)
  - Photographs of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 81)
  - Photographs of the Calorimeter, animals, and experiments, undated (Box 82)
- Publications, 9
  - Agricultural Bulletins Number 1-16, 1882-1886; Textual Bound Volumes (Box 1)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station Reports, 1888-1906 (Box 1)
  - Penn State Agricultural Experiment Station Annual Reports, 1919-1964 (Box 12)
  - National Research Council Special Bulletin, 1945, May 28 (Box 30)
  - National Research Council - Reports, 1940-1943 (Box 30)
  - National Research Council - Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 30)
  - Publications by Thorne M. Carpenter, 1909 - 1938 (Box 9)
  - The Nutritive Evaluation of Forages (by R. W. Swift), 1956 (Box 17)
  - Bio/Medical Instrumentation Magazine, 1964 (Box 17)
  - French Article - U.S. Department of AG., 1927 (Box 49)
  - Booklet - The FFA (Future Farmers of America) at Fifty, 1979 (Box 49)
  - PA. Attitude Inventory for Hunter and Firearm Safety, 1972 (Box 49)
  - Wildlife Review, 1938 (Box 27)
  - The Energy Metabolism of Cattle in Relation to the Plane of Nutrition (article), 1928 (Box 27)
- Tests, 10
  - Blank Test - H2O and CO2 - Meters 1 and 3, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - CO2 and H2O with Meter Measurements In/Out, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - CO2 and H2O and Heat Blank Test on Chamber, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - H2O and CO2 - Meters 1 and 3, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - Meter Factors, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - CO2/H2O/Heat, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - with Heat from Lightbulbs, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - Air Meters, 1957 (Box 9)
  - Blank Tests - CO2 Recovery and H2O, 1957 (Box 9)
  - Blank Tests, 1927 (Box 27)
  - Blank Tests, 1937 (Box 27)
  - Test With New Air Using CO2 Apparatus, 1911 (Box 2)
  - Test With Wet and Dry Bulbs in Outcoming Air Current, 1911 (Box 2)
  - Test of Preservatives on Urine, undated (Box 17)
  - Test - Soda Lime, 1926 (Box 17)
  - Test - CO2 Recovery, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - Comparison of Meters, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Blank Test - Ventilation, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Test - Methane Recovery, 1946-1947 (Box 9)
  - Tests - Calorimeter, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Blank Tests, 1948 (Box 9)
  - Test - CO2 Check, 1946 and 1948 (Box 9)
  - Testing of U Tubes, undated (Box 14)
  - Experiment 935 B - Tube Weights, undated (Box 7)
  - Blank Test, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Test Run - Steer 11, 1937 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank, 1902-1903 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank, 1904-1905 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank/Electrical, 1906 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank/Marsh Gas, 1907 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank, 1908 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol, 1909 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank, 1911-1913 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol, 1914-1919 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank, 1920-1921 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol, 1922 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Blank, 1923 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol/Blank, 1924-1926 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Blank/Furnaces, 1927 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Alcohol, 1928 (Box 14)
  - Tests: Blank, 1931 (Box 14)
  - TB Tests on Animals, 1892-1906 (Box 53)
  - Test - CO2 Check, 1946 (Box 27)
  - Tests of Wet and Dry Bulb Thermometers, 1911 (Box 30)
  - Tests of Thermometers in Water Bath, 1912 (Box 30)
  - Tests: Heat Measurements - Light Bulbs in the Chamber of the Calorimeter, 1955 (Box 9)
  - Tests - CO2 Recovery Check, 1951, 1958-1959 (Box 9)
  - Tests - Blank Calorimeter Runs, 1937 (Box 27)
  - Spirometer - Alcohol Test, 1932 (Box 30)